thelotter.com 2015-06-27

# Lottery Rules | Online Lottery Policy | theLotter

|  |   
| 

This is the privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") that governs how we, The Lotter Enterprises Ltd. ("theLotter", "we", "our" or "us"), use Personal Information (defined below) that we collect, receive and store about individuals who visit or use the website www.theLotter.com (together with its sub-domains, content and services, the "Site"). This Privacy Policy forms part of the Terms of Use, available at www.theLotter.com/terms-of-use/ (the "Terms").

  1. Introduction 

1.1. 

Personal Information. We have implemented this Privacy Policy because your privacy, and the privacy of other Site users, is important to us. We provide this Privacy Policy explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your Personal Information is collected and used in connection with the Site and certain services that we offer through or in connection with the Site. “Personal Information” means any information that may be used, either alone or in combination with other information, to personally identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a personal profile, an email address, a home or other physical address, or other contact information.

1.2. 

English and Translated Versions. If you are reading a translation of this Privacy Policy in a language other than English, you acknowledge and agree that (i) the English version is the official version; (ii) the non-English version is provided for your convenience only and the translation will not be valid as an agreement; and (iii) in the event of any inconsistency between the English and a non-English version, the English version will prevail and govern.

1.3. 

Consent and Modification. By using the Site, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to theLotter's processing of Personal Information for the purposes set forth herein. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time; if we do so we will notify you by email, to your designated email address, or we will post the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Any such change shall become effective ten (10) days following the notification and your continued use of the Site thereafter means that you accept those changes.

  2. What Personal Information We Collect and How We Collect It. 

We do not currently require you to provide Personal Information in order to have access to general information available on the Site. But, we do receive and/or collect information from you in the following ways: 

2.1. 

Account. In order to provide you with certain services via the Site, you may be required to create an account (“Account”). When you create an Account you will be asked to provide us with certain mandatory information such as your first name, your user name, your external email address (such as a Hotmail or Gmail account), and a password that you will use for your Account.

2.2. 

Services. We may collect, receive and store Personal Information in connection with certain services that we provide on and via the Site. Such information may include your name, external email address, and mobile phone number. If you participate in our Tell-A-Friend Service then you will disclose to us, and we will receive, the email addresses of your friends that you wish to refer to the Site (each a "Friend"). Your participation in any services is optional and you at all times have the choice of choosing whether to provide any related Personal Information.

2.3. 

Transfers of Payments to You. You may be entitled to have us transfer certain amounts of money to you (for example, in connection with lottery winnings). To the extent that we do so, you will first be required to provide us certain Personal Information regarding your preferred payment method. Such information could include your bank account or credit card name and number. 

2.4. 

Purchases. The Site may include the option to purchase certain products or services from us. If you choose to so purchase a product or services from us we will require sufficient information from you to complete the transaction. Such information could include a credit card number and related account and billing information, invoice related information, and other data required to process the order. We may also update such data should you grant us permission to bill you or your credit card for recurring charges, such as monthly or other types of periodic payments. We may use the tools, software or services of third party service providers to process transactions on our behalf, in which case you acknowledge and agree to review and be bound by the terms of use and privacy policy of said third-party service provider. Except as set forth herein, we will not share your financial Personal Information with any third person or entity.

2.5. 

Identification and Verification Information. In order to participate in some services (such as withdrawing or depositing money from or to your Account), it may be necessary to first provide us with certain identification and verification information that we require in order to process your request. Such information may include a copy of your passport, driver's license, national identity card, a utility bill (for proof of address), and/or a copy of the front and back of your credit card that you are using in connection with your Account (we request that you cover and do not send us the credit card code verification (CVV) number; if we receive your CVV number we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete and not store it and may ask that you resubmit a copy of your credit card without the CVV number being visible). 

2.6. 

'Contact Us' Information. If you send us a "contact us" or "chat with us" request, whether by submitting an online form that we make available or by using an online tool or email address that we provide, you may be required to provide us with certain information such as your first name and an external email address. You may also choose to disclose other Personal Information.

2.7. 

Log Files. The Site may make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, clicked pages and any other information your browser may send to us. We may use such information to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the Site, and gather demographic information. 

2.8. 

Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies. Some of our Site pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Site activity. Certain cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Site user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser.

  3. The Way We Use Personal Information. 

If you submit or we collect Personal Information through the Site, then such Personal Information may be used in the following ways: 

3.1.

We will use your Personal Information to provide and improve our Site and services to you, to contact you in connection with the Site and certain services or products that you may have registered for, and to identify and authenticate your access to the parts of the Site and services that you are authorized to access. 

3.2.

We may use your designated external email address to send you updates, a newsletter or news regarding the Site and our products and services.

3.3.

We may use your Personal Information to contact you in response to a "contact us" or "chat with us" request.

3.4.

If you chose to invite your Friend(s) to the Site, we will use the contact information that you provide us to automatically send your Friend(s) a one-time email inviting them to visit the Site, register a Site account, and participate in our services. The email that we send will include opt-out information to avoid receiving future emails from us. We will include your name in the invitation email. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending the one-time invitation email and tracking the success of whether your Friend registers a Site account and purchases a lottery ticket via the site. Your Friend may (i) contact us at [support@theLotter.com](mailto:service@theLotter.com) to request that we do not store this information; and/or (ii) choose to avoid receiving future invitation emails from us by following the opt-out instructions within the invitation email.

3.5.

We may transfer your Personal Information within theLotter, and to our subsidiaries and affiliated companies, but only for the purpose of providing our services to you. Such information may be transferred to other countries around the world. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy.

3.6.

We may transfer your Personal Information to our third party service providers, but only to provide our services to you or for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. Such information may be transferred to other countries around the world. We use commercially reasonable efforts to only engage or interact with third party service providers that post a privacy policy governing their processing of Personal Information.

3.7.

We may disclose your Personal Information or any information you submitted via the Site if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is helpful or reasonably necessary to (i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; (ii) enforce our Terms including investigations of potential violations thereof; (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud or security issues; or (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of theLotter, its users, yourself or the public.

  4. Use of Anonymous Information. 

4.1. 

We may use Anonymous Information (as defined below) or disclose it to third party service providers in order to improve our services and enhance your experience with the Site. We may also disclose Anonymous Information (with or without compensation) to third parties, including advertisers and partners, for purposes including, but not limited to, targeting advertisements. "Anonymous Information" means information which does not enable identification of an individual user, such as aggregated information about the use of our Site.

  5. Opting-Out. 

5.1. 

If you wish to stop receiving promotional, advertising, or activity-related emails from us to your external email address, you may remove yourself from the relevant mailing list at any time by following the instructions within each email that you receive from us (at any time you may use the tools provided in your Account to recommence receiving such emails). Please note that even if you opt-out of receiving emails to your external email address you may still receive messages from us to your Site account. 

5.2. 

If you have elected to receive SMS alerts from us, you may use the tools provided in your Account to stop receiving such SMS alerts (you may also use the same tools to recommence receiving SMS alerts to your mobile phone number at any time).

  6. Choice. 

6.1. 

At all times, you may choose whether or not to provide or disclose Personal Information. The notices that we provide on the Site in circumstances where we collect Personal Information should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you may still visit parts of the Site, but you may be unable to access certain options, programs, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you. 

  7. Access/Accuracy. 

7.1. 

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, theLotter wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. You may enter your Account and update or delete your details at any time.

  8. Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites. 

8.1. 

We may use a reputable third party to present or serve advertisements that you may see on the Site. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy. 

  9. Links to Other Sites. 

9.1. 

The Site may contain links to third party websites that are not owned or controlled by theLotter. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of third party websites, and you visit them at your own risk. 

  10. Children's Privacy. 

10.1. 

The Site is not structured to attract individuals under the age of 18. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 18 years. 

  11. Security. 

11.1. 

The security of Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards, including the use of appropriate administrative, physical and technical safeguards, to protect the Personal Information that we collect from you. To the extent that we collect sensitive Personal Information from you (for example, your credit card number or other financial Personal Information), we use SSL encryption to protect that information. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on the Site, you can contact us a [support@theLotter.com](mailto:service@theLotter.com).

  12. In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy. 

12.1. 

In the event that theLotter is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign Personal Information that we have collected as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used. In any of the circumstances described in this paragraph, the information will be subject to the privacy policy of the purchaser or assignee.

  13. Your California Privacy Rights. 

13.1. 

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of theLotter who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [support@theLotter.com](mailto:service@theLotter.com). Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year. 

  14. Commitment. 

14.1. 

We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and we are constantly evolving our Site to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@theLotter.com](mailto:service@theLotter.com). 

  15. Facebook Connect. 

15.1. 

You may engage with our content, such as video, lottery games, applications, and other offerings, through third-party social networking sites, such as Facebook. When you engage with our content on or through third party social networking sites, plug-ins or applications, you may allow us to have access to certain information from your public social media profile to deliver the content or as part of the operation of the application. 

Last update: August 2014 

|  |   
  |   |
